Juanita Kidd Stout Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Subject File, circa 1900-1998 (Box 75-93)
  - Biographical file (Box 76)
    - Lawyers
      - “S” miscellaneous, 1963-1986, 1992-1997
      - Thomas, Clarence
        - Articles and newspaper clippings, 1991-1998, undated, (3 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1991-1993, undated
        - Writ, 1994 (Box 80)
      - Thomas, Lowell L., 1987-1988, undated
      - “T” miscellaneous, 1982-1985
      - White, Ronald Avon
        - Family papers
          - Miscellany, 1983, 1992, undated
          - White, Ronald Ali, 1984-1987, undated
          - White, Santi, 1984-1987, undated
          - White, Simone, 1979-1983, undated
        - Miscellany, 1976-1998, undated
      - “W-Y” miscellaneous, 1978-1995, (2 folders)
    - Logan, Thomas W. C., 1984
    - “L” miscellaneous, 1982-1985
    - Moore, Cleo H., 1964-1968, undated
    - “M” miscellaneous, 1961, 1976, 1983-1985, 1994 (Box 81)
    - Nelson, Gail, 1962-1969, 1977-1997, undated, (4 folders)
    - “N-R” miscellaneous, 1985-1997
    - Sullivan, Leon, 1980-1985, undated
    - “S-Y” miscellaneous, 1931-1996, (4 folders)
  - Civil rights organizations, 1960, 1970-1971, 1982-1994, undated
  - Colorado Committee for Women's History, undated (Box 82)
  - Corporate publications directed to African Americans, 1964, 1977, undated
  - Democratic and Republican parties, 1964-1978, 1992, undated
  - Humor
    - Cartoons, 1982-1988, undated, (3 folders)
    - Jokes and other textual material, 1970-1995, undated, (3 folders)
  - Josephson Institute for the Advancement of Ethics, Los Angeles, Calif.
    - Ethics in Action, 1989-1995
    - Miscellany, 1985-1989 (Box 83)
  - The Links
    - Chronological file, 1980-1998, undated, (3 folders)
    - Constitutions, bylaws, and manuals of procedure, 1981-1982, undated
    - The Journal, 1983
    - Link to Link, 1983
    - Links Foundation, 1983, undated
    - Penne Towne chapter, Philadelphia, Pa.
      - Miscellany, 1995-1997, undated
      - Histories, 1993-1995, (2 folders)
    - Project Discovery, undated (Box 84)
  - National 4-H Council, 1967, 1990, undated
  - National Coalition of 100 Black Women, 1982-1985, undated
  - National Epicureans
    - Conclave programs, 1989-1994
    - Miscellany, 1989-1994, undated
  - New Voice and Viewpoint, 1985
  - Oklahoma and the Southwestern United States
    - Articles and newspaper clippings, 1966, 1981-1992, undated
    - Miscellany, 1997, undated
    - Tulsa, Okla., 1990-1997, undated
    - Urban League of Greater Oklahoma City, 1989
    - Wewoka, Okla., 1945, 1981-1987, undated
  - Philadelphia Cotillion Society, Philadelphia, Pa., 1968
  - Philadelphia General Hospital Charitable Foundation, Philadelphia, Pa., 1984
  - Philadelphia Ranger Corps, 1990-1992 (Box 85)
  - Philadelphia Tribune, 1959, 1992
  - Photographs and drawings
    - Stout, Juanita Kidd, 1923-1995, undated, (2 folders)
    - Others, circa 1900-1995, undated, (2 folders)
  - Pride Magazine, 1970 (Box 86)
  - Religion file
    - Baptist churches, 1980, 1987
    - Christian Methodist Episcopal Church, 1970-1973
    - Episcopal church
      - African Americans, 1968, 1990-1995, undated
      - Church of the Holy Trinity, Philadelphia, Pa.
        - Chronological file, 1990-1996, undated
        - Parish directories, 1989-1991
        - Parish profile, 1997
      - Eisenstadt, Elizabeth, 1990-1991, undated
    - Miscellany, 1951, 1981-1995, undated
  - Russian children's books, 1978
  - Schools, colleges, and universities
    - Davidson, Arthur T., speech, “The Role of the Historic Black Colleges in the Training of Black Professionals,” 1982
    - Delaware State College, Dover, Del., 1987-1990
    - Delaware Valley Consortium on Drugs and Alcohol, 1983-1985, undated
    - Douglass High School, Wewoka, Okla.
      - Correspondence, 1985, 1991-1995
      - Douglass Tribune, 1936
      - Miscellany, 1931-1935, 1948, 1961, 1975-1976, 1985-1996, undated, (2 folders) (Box 87)
      - Photographs, 1931-1945, undated
      - Speeches, 1935, 1983-1985, undated
    - Florida Agricultural and Mechanical University, Tallahassee, Fla., 1948
      - 1984-1987, undated
    - Fisk University, Nashville, Tenn.
      - Miscellany, 1964, 1987-1989, 1991, undated, (2 folders)
      - Ponder, Henry, 1985-1986, undated
    - Grade schools and grade school systems, 1961-1996
    - Homecoming: The Historically Black College Alumni and Campus Newspaper, 1989-1992 (Box 88)
    - Indiana University, Bloomington, Ind.
      - Commencements, 1948, 1966, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1966-1998
      - Neal-Marshall Alumni Club, 1981-1997
    - Lincoln University, Jefferson City, Mo., 1936, 1960, 1976-1979, 1994, undated
    - Lincoln University, Lincoln University, Pa., 1986-1997, undated, (2 folders)
    - Mary Holmes College, West Point, Miss., 1987
    - Miscellaneous colleges and universities, 1964-1993, (3 folders) (Box 89)
    - Morgan State University, Baltimore, Md., 1985-1997
    - Oklahoma State University, Stillwater, Okla.
      - Miscellany, 1975-1981, 1988-1989
      - Outreach, 1979
    - University of Iowa, Iowa City, Iowa, 1965-1995, undated
    - Sears, Roebuck and Co., 1986
  - The Set (social club), 1990 (Box 90)
  - Sororities and fraternities
    - Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority, 1968-1969, undated
    - Delta Sigma Theta Sorority
      - Chronological file, 1945, 1955-1997, undated, (3 folders)
      - Constitutions, bylaws, handbooks, and rituals, 1939-1940, 1990-1992
      - Delta Research and Educational Foundations, 1989-1995, undated
      - Miscellany, 1946, 1976-1996, undated
      - National publications (Box 91)
        - Delta Newsletter, 1975-1994, (4 folders)
        - Delta Update, 1992-1993
      - Philadelphia, Pa., alumnae chapter publications
        - Crimson and Cream Chronicle, 1989-1994
        - Newsletters, 1991-1996
      - Speeches, 1951, undated
    - Kappa Alpha Psi Fraternity, 1976-1985, 1991-1995, (2 folders)
  - SOS-Kinderdorf International, 1960-1965, 1989, undated (Box 92)
  - Tobacco companies, fact books regarding African Americans, 1977, undated
  - Trips
    - Africa
      - Kenya independence
        - Delegate briefing book, 1963
        - Miscellany, 1963, undated
        - Print and near print material, 1963
      - Lecture tour, Kenya and Nigeria
        - After trip report, 1967
        - Correspondence, 1966-1967
        - Itineraries, lists, and information sheets, 1966-1967, undated
      - Lecture tour, six countries
        - Miscellany, 1967, undated
        - Printed matter, 1965-1969, undated
    - Miscellany, 1956, 1986-1987
    - People to People International
      - Women judges trip to China and Japan
        - Articles, 1976-1982, undated
        - Background material, 1976-1982, undated (Box 93)
        - Correspondence, 1982-1983, undated
        - Information bulletins, 1980-1983, undated
        - Pugh, Ann, trip diary, 1983
    - World Affairs Council of Philadelphia, Philadelphia, Pa., Canadian trip, 1977-1979, undated
  - United States Air Force, 1990, undated
  - United States Department of Energy, “Black Contributors to Science and Technology,” poster, undated
  - “Woman Suffrage Party,” pennant, undated
  - Women's Historical Philadelphia, a Walking Tour, undated
  - Young Women's Christian Association of Philadelphia, Philadelphia, Pa. undated
- Speeches and Writings File, 1935-1997 (Box 93-101)
  Articles, speeches, event programs, printed matter, and miscellaneous material.
  Arranged by type of material and thereunder chronologically.
  - Articles (Box 93)
    - 1959-1985, (2 folders)
    - 1989-1993, undated, (2 folders) (Box 94)
  - Miscellany, undated
  - Speaking engagements
    - 1959-1987, (5 folders)
    - 1989-1997, undated, (4 folders) (Box 95)
  - Speech file
    - 1935, 1950, 1963-1976, (5 folders)
    - 1977-1985, (6 folders) (Box 96)
    - 1986-1997, undated, (10 folders) (Box 97)
    - Undated, (5 folders); (3 folders); (4 folders) (Box 98, Box 99, Box 100, Box 101)
- Oversize, 1962-1964 (Box OV 1)
  Docket, Municipal Court, Philadelphia County, Pa.
  - Legal File (Box OV 1)
    - Municipal Court, Philadelphia County, Pa.
      - Docket, 1962-1964 (Container 57)